Ana Bollain

Front-end Developer





About me

Curious by nature, I define myself as persevering and resourceful. With great adaptability, my empathy, collaborative attitude and commitment make me a great team player.

Thanks to over 6 years of work experience in France and Spain, I have mastered both project planning and stress management to meet client expectations with tight deadlines.

Soft skills

Teamwork

Empathy

Problem Solving

Attention to detail

Creative Thinking

Responsiveness

Adaptability

Management

Projects

Rick & Morty Personal Project | React JS

Legacy JS Code Upgrading 👄 Team Project | React JS & Node JS

Awesome Profile Cards Team Project | Javascript

Personal Project | Javascript

We are the Ada's 👄 Personal Project | Javascript

Monsterous Battle 👄 Personal Project | Javascript

Work Experience

Front-end Developer

Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- > Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Responsive Design, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- > Javascript (ES6) and creation of a SPA application with React.
- > Developing a basic REST API with Node JS and Express JS.
- > SQLite for creating and managing databases and EJS Template Engine.
- > Version control with Git.
- > Project development under SCRUM framework and Agile philosophy.
- > Development tools: Gulp, Visual Studio Code, Terminal, Zeplin.
- > Communication skills and team work: Slack, Github, Railway.

Partner Architect & Freelance Interior Designer

Freelance. Remote | March 2022 - Oct. 2022

Estudi Biga SCCLP. Barcelona | Sept. 2019 - March 2022

Katty Schiebeck. Barcelona | April 2019 - Oct. 2019

- > Management and development of projects as a team leader.
- > Coordination of all parties involved for project decision-making.
- > Design, illustration and 3D rendering of creative proposals.
- > Production of techinal and administrative documentation.
- > Adaptabilty to tigtht deadlines with high quality standards.

Architect & Interior Designer

Atelier du Pont. Paris | Jan. 2017 - March 2019

AWP. París | March 2016 - Oct. 2016

- > Contact with clients in oral presentations and project follow-up.
- > Analysis of commercial proposals and compliance with client's budget.
- > Contact with sales representatives for the prescription of materials.
- > Management and development of residential and hospitality projects.

Education

Intensive Front-end Development Bootcamp

Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

Online Web Development Courses

Platzi | Remote | July 2022 - Sept. 2022

HTML5 & CSS3 | CSS Grid | Javascript | JS Engine (V8) & Browser

Basics of Web Development & Coding

Coursera. University of Michigan | Remote | April 2022 - June 2022

Master of Architecture

ETSAM. Polytechnic University of Madrid | Sept. 2008 - July 2015

Architecture & Landscape Exchange Program

KTH. Sweden | Erasmus | Sept. 2012 - July 2013

Technical Skills Languages

\odot	HTML5	\bigcirc	Gulp	Spanish
\bigcirc	CSS3	\bigcirc	Git	Native
\bigcirc	Sass	\bigcirc	Agile	English
\bigcirc	Javascript	\bigcirc	Scrum	Professional. C1 Advanced (CAE)
\bigcirc	React JS	\bigcirc	InDesign	French
\bigcirc	Node JS	\bigcirc	Illustrator	Fluent
\bigcirc	SQLite	\bigcirc	Photoshop	Basque

Native, EGA